(Howard:)and license it to companies
that make guidance systems.
(Raj:)Look at that. You've known
you're gonna be a father
(Raj:)for less than a day
and you're already stepping up.
(Leonard:)I'm telling you,
you got this.
(Howard:)Maybe you're right.
(Sheldon:)Of course he's right.
(Sheldon:)You and I both know how hard it
is growing up without a father.
(Sheldon:)That's why I'm confident
you're gonna be
(Sheldon:)the best dad you can be.
(Howard:)Thank you, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)You're welcome.
(Sheldon:)And if he has
twins, we can do
(Sheldon:)all kinds
of neat experiments on them.
(Bernadette:)You guys can go in
if you want.
(Penny:)No, we're a team.
(Penny:)If you can't go in,
we're not going in.
(Amy:)Then why are we drinking?
(Penny:)Okay, it's not like she's got
the Christ child in there,
(Penny:)all right?
(Penny:)Oh. It's Leonard.
(Penny:)He says Sheldon's drunk
and they're gonna do karaoke
(Penny:)if we want to join them.
(Bernadette:)That sounds fun.
(Sheldon:)Oh, no.
(Penny:)Sheldon's drunk
texting me.
(Penny:)What's it say?